springahead.com 2019-01-28

# 

* * *

We at SpringAhead take your privacy seriously. By visiting the www.SpringAhead.com websites and domain names, or otherwise accessing any other linked pages, features, content, products, services or installed applications offered by us, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### What does this privacy policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers SpringAhead's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that SpringAhead gathers when you access the Website and when you use SpringAhead's services or applications. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SpringAhead does not own or control, or to individuals that SpringAhead does not employ or manage.

#### Personal Information You Provide to Us

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include your full name, email address, IP address, browser information, username, password and any other information necessary for us to provide our services.

#### Personal Information Collected Automatically

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or use our services. SpringAhead automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested.

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Website and its components. SpringAhead only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

#### Data Ownership

Any data you submit while using the SPRINGAHEAD website or a SPRINGAHEAD service belongs to you. You may remove it at any time. If you ask SPRINGAHEAD to delete your account, SPRINGAHEAD shall make commercially reasonable efforts to remove all of your data from its servers. Despite such removal efforts, portions of your data may remain on SPRINGAHEAD's production and back-up servers indefinitely.

Any information you submit that can identify you personally on a blog, bulletin board or chat room through the SPRINGAHEAD website or a SPRINGAHEAD service can be viewed and used by other SPRINGAHEAD users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. SPRINGAHEAD is not responsible for your disclosure of this information in these forums.

#### Protecting Your Data

Every precaution is taken to insure the security of your data while using the SPRINGAHEAD website or a SPRINGAHEAD service. SPRINGAHEAD uses industry-standard firewalls, secure web servers (https), data encryption and authentication procedures, among other techniques, to maintain the security of your data and your online session.

#### Access

Upon request SPRINGAHEAD will provide you with information about whether or not SPRINGAHEAD holds any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging in to your account, contacting your SPRINGAHEAD Account Manager, or by contacting us at support@SPRINGAHEAD.com. SPRINGAHEAD will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

SPRINGAHEAD acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. SPRINGAHEAD has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to the SPRINGAHEAD's client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

In certain circumstances SPRINGAHEAD may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service.

#### Policy Changes

SPRINGAHEAD reserves the right at its sole discretion to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. You may review updates to SPRINGAHEAD's Terms of Use Agreement and/or Privacy Policy at any time via links on SPRINGAHEAD's website. You agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of any revised Terms of Use Agreement and/or Privacy Policy on the SPRINGAHEAD website, and you agree that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the revisions to the Terms of Use Agreement and/or Privacy Policy, as applicable. If SPRINGAHEAD makes any material changes we shall notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective.

#### Contact Information

Feel free to contact us for any reason, including a request to be added to or taken off an email list, or if you have any questions or concerns. Please provide your company's name in addition to your name and title.

**BY POSTAL MAIL**  
525 Second Street.  
San Francisco, CA 94107

**BY PHONE**  
800-874-1118

**BY EMAIL**  

#### Communications from SpringAhead

**TO UNSUBSCRIBE FROM SPRINGAHEAD EMAIL**  
If for any reason you would like to unsubscribe from our marketing and promotional email programs, simply click the Unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of the email you receive OR send us an email at [support@springahead.com](mailto:support@springahead.com)

If you no longer wish to receive administrative and customer-service-related email messages, you must deactivate your SpringAhead account. If you are not the administrator of your SpringAhead account, please consult your account Administrator for updating or removing your account.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SpringAhead may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.
